嘿 你好
Hey, now.
我们之前打了电话 他们说你醒了...
We called earlier, they said you were up...
等我们赶到这里 你又睡了过去
And by the time we get here, you're back asleep.
等了很久了?
Been there long?
没有
No.
20分钟
20 minutes.
你瞧 我们实在不想打搅你
You know, we didn't want to exactly disturb you.
我才闷死了呢
I'm bored, is all.
是啊 不过还是...
Yeah, but still.
那么 你们有什么要问我的
So, what you got for me?
认照片?
Spreads?
是的
Yeah.
Little Man 我肯定
Little Man. For sure.
很好 你能签名吗?
That's good. Are you able to write?
好的 二号
Okay. Number two.
我能指认Little Man
I can make Little Man,
因为他冲在前面...
Because he's in the front...
想抢走仪表盘上的那些现金
Trying to snatch the cash off the dashboard.
但是另一个 他在外面的暗处
But the other one, he's outside in the dark.
所以...
So....
那么 你瞧...没事
So, you know, it's okay.
没事
It's okay.
那这里还有谁你认得的吗?
Is there anyone here that you do recognize?
有的 Wee-Bey
Sure. Wee-Bey.
好吧
All right.
让我来告诉你 我们掌握的枪手情况
Let me tell you where we're coming from with the shooters.
我们追踪了他们的逃跑线路
We tracked their escape route,
Landsman发现了他们的连帽衣
And Landsman came up with their hoodies.
现在 DNA结果也匹配了...
Now, DNA matched...
其中一件连帽衣里的头发属于Wee-Bey
Human hair from one of the hoodies to Wee-Bey.
Freamon 他追踪了 现场附近的一部公用电话
Freamon, he tracked a call from the pay phone near the scene,
呼叫的是Stringer Bell的呼机
To Stringer Bell's pager.
而那个打电话的人 用的是Bey的呼叫代号
Now, the caller was using Bey's beeper code.
鉴证科 他们从电话机附近
Crime lab, they lift a print...
一个苏打水罐头上 提取了一枚属于Little Man的指纹
Off a soda can near that phone, and that matches Little Man.
所以 你瞧
You know, so,
你瞧 我是说...
You know, I'm saying....
好吧 听我说
Okay, hear me out.
不妙的是
There's a downside here.
我们没有找到枪
We don't have the guns...
案发现场没有指纹 没有目击者
No prints from the scene, no witnesses.
更糟的是 我们要面对Baltimore市的陪审团
But worse, we're going to be dealing with a Baltimore city jury...
而想在镇上找到一个好人原本就很难
And a good man is hard to find in this town.
特别是 要同时找到12个
Twelve of them together, especially.
如果把对你开枪的人都指认了...
An ID of both your shooters...
可以让官司顺利很多
Will play a whole lot easier come trial.
嗯
Yeah.
有时候 我们一定要搏一搏
Sometimes things just got to play hard.
火线重案组 第一季 第十三集 审判
The Wire S01E13 Sentencing
第一季演唱:The Blind Boys of Alabama
Way Down in the Hole
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"一切都在游戏里..."  ---Baltimore老西区
我们把名单上的都抓了 除了CCO
We got everyone on our list except C.C.O.
是的 我们突袭了他母亲的房子...
We hit his mama's house...
她说他去了Wasbash 为了出庭什么的
And she says that he went up to Wabash for some court date.
你可以上电脑查查
You can get on the computer and see
有没有庭警可以在哪个法庭逮住他
If any of the Sheriff's deputie can snatch him up in some courtroom.
好的
Yeah.
不 不 我们抓住了Ronnie Moe
No, we got Ronnie Moe.
我现在正看着他坐进囚车里呢
I'm looking at him go in the jail van right now.
好的
All right.
- 满载而归 我们回去吧 - "长官"
- Fished our limit. Let's go home. - "Sir."
- 啊? - 要说"我们回去吧 长官"
- Huh? - "Let's go home, sir."
你正看着一位将被任命的警司
You're looking at a soon-to-be-made sergeant.
所以 我要说的是 我们在巡警里走动的时候
So what I'm saying is, when we're around the troops...
你得习惯表达你应有的尊敬
You got to get used to showing the proper respect.
所以 "我们回去吧 长官" 明白了吗?
So, "Let's go home, sir." All right?
已逮捕
抓住了几个?
What's the count?
目前为止我们抓了12个
So far we've picked up 12.
还有7个在逃
That leaves seven on the wing.
还有什么有价值的?
Anything worthwhile?
一些电话号码对上了
Some phone numbers that match,
一些绰号也是 其他没什么了
Scraps of nicknames, not much else.
我们现在需要点突破
We need something now.
除非我们马上拿出点新的线索
They'll shut us down unless we come up
否则他们会立即解散我们
With something fresh to run with right now.
监听线已经断了
The wires are dead.
在俱乐部装的窃听器也没了用
The bug in the club is useless.
我们去抓人的时候 他们就已经转移了
They're moving out of there even as we got up on them.
- 去了哪里? - 不知道
- To where? - No clue.
但是他们肯定会东山再起
But they're going to have to set up again.
要么Barksdale重建分销网 要么就放弃高楼区
Either Barksdale moves to reset his distribution or he gives up the towers.
- 就算没有Avon 还有Stringer - 为什么不是Avon?
- If not Avon, then Stringer. - And why not Avon?
因为没有前科 他两小时前就被保释了
With no priors, he's out two hours after the bail review.
我们对Barksdale的指控 很难真动得了他
What we put on Barksdale barely makes him break stride.
好吧 那么我们预感他们会东山再起
Okay, so we get a hint of where they're setting back up.
我们向检察官提出新的窃听行动...
We ask the State's Attorney for a new bug...
如果能确定电话 也许再实施一次监听
Maybe even a wire if we get onto a phone.
除非副局翘了 这才有可能
Not while the deputy breathes air.
在你打完你的宣誓书前 我们就都被调走了
We'll be reassigned before you finish typing up your affidavit.
那联邦调查局呢?
How about the feds?
你觉得副局会让你把这个娄子 捅到联邦调查局去吗?
You think the Deputy's going to let you take this mess federal?
为什么要让副局知道呢?
Why does the Deputy need to know?
McNulty 你真是个人才
McNulty, you are a piece of work.
McNulty
McNulty.
喂?
Yeah?
不会吧
No shit.
它妈的不会吧
No fucking shit.
是Rhonda Pearlman
It's Rhonda Pearlman.
她刚接到来自新泽西北部 一个公共辩护律师助理的电话
She just got a call from an assistant public defender in North Jersey...
声称为一个叫 D'Angelo Barksdale的人辩护
Who claims to represent a man by the name of D'Angelo Barksdale.
凶杀科见 带上录音机
Meet me in Homicide. Bring a tape recorder.
没有毒贩的律师? Levy没出现?
No drug lawyers? No Levy?
案子自己"长脚了" 不是吗?
Case got some legs on her, don't she?
不是吗?
Don't she?
25万的保释金 他妈的你相信吗
Quarter of a million dollars bail. You believe that shit?
光是把这么多钱掏出来 都让人肉疼
It hurts to even show that kind of money.
Levy在哪儿? 他没在俱乐部 是吧?
Where Levy at? He ain't at the club, is he?
我不知道 不 俱乐部暴露了 我们不能在那儿谈事了
I don't know. No, club's out. We can't talk there no more.
好了 伙计 让我们离开这里
Come on, man, let's get out of here.
怎么样 哥们
What's up, baby?
那就这样了?
So, this is it?
瞧 在你去任何地方 在任何地方谈话之前...
Look, before you go anyplace else, before you talk anyplace else...
我们得好好想一想
We got to think this through.
最新情况 我们有接近20个人被捕
We're up to almost 20 arrests at last count.
如果看一下那些逮捕理由 都和你的很像
And if you look at the probable cause, they all read just like yours:
来自一条秘密的线报
Information from a confidential source.
一个告密能搞得这样天翻地覆?
Don't this seem way too much for one snitch?
我同意 我直觉是有人在监听
I agree. My gut tells me a wire.
要么是一两部电话
Either a phone or two,
也许是在房子的某个角落安装了什么
Or maybe something in a room somewhere.
你有在电话上和你的侄子 说过新泽西的事吗?
Talked to your nephew on the phone about the Jersey thing?
不 当然没有了 绝不在电话里说
No. Of course not, man. No phones.
我告诉他的时候 是面对面地谈的
When I talk to him, I talk to him face-to-face,
在俱乐部后面 我的办公室里
In my office, in the back of the club.
操
Fuck.
你们搬出那里是明智的
It's good you moved out of there.
我不知道 伙计 如果他们在那里搞了个麦克风...
I don't know, man. I mean, if they got a mike up in there...
他们就听去了所有 我跟你之间说过的事
They got you and me saying all kind of shit.
这个让我想起来了
That reminds me.
Bay留言:需要回电
他说他今晚在
He said he'd be in tonight.
事实是 他们抓了你 却没有动我?
Thing is, they take you and leave me?
是啊 我也它妈的搞不懂了 伙计
That's what's fucking me up, too, man.
瞧 我们很快会知道 只要我开始进行调查
Look, we'll know soon enough, as soon as I start pressing for discovery.
同时 你想怎么处理那些被关起来的人?
What do you want to do about the people they locked up?
我们得把他们弄出来
We got to pull them.
那得花一大笔钱
That's showing a lot of money.
否则 我们就得冒着倒戈的风险
If we don't, we run the risk of making them enemies.
说到这个 你和你的侄子怎么了?
Speaking of which, where are you with your nephew?
他到底有没有醒悟?
Is he going to see the light or what?
让我告诉你 哥们 他是自己人 明白吗
Let me tell you something, man. He family, all right?
他不会乱说的
He not going to buck.
在新泽西的牢里呆个一两天 他就会哭爹喊娘...
A day or two in the New Jersey bullpen, he gonna be crying...
等着他的保释金 像我们其他人一样
Waiting for bail money like the rest of them.
好吧
All right.
那么 我们从亲戚那调遣这笔钱 可以隐蔽点
So, let's run the money through the families, that'll hide it some.
- 不要让同一个做担保 - 好的
- And don't use the same bondsman. - All right.
瞧 伙计们 我知道说这个有点早...
Look, gentlemen, I know it's early...
不过我希望你们能开始考虑让谁顶罪...
I want you to start thinking about who was charged...
他们愿意坐多久的牢
And what kind of time they can do.
有一种让你减少暴露的方法 称作结构式抗辩
One of the ways to limit your exposure is what's called a structured plea.
那意味着 你现在一定要把你的人
That means that you're going to have to deliver your people...
全部手下 都放到一个人名下
All of them, down to a man.
我今天见到了你的姑娘 为了做指认
I saw your girl today, for the idents.
她怎么样?
How's she doing?
还好吧 我猜
Okay, I guess.
她已经离开了重症看护室
She's out of the ICU.
虽然恢复得慢 但在康复中
Moving slow, but moving, you know?
Jimmy 你还没有去看过她吧?
Jimmy, you ain't been to see her?
没有 我没法走进去
No. I couldn't go in.
看她不是为了你自己 懂吗?
This ain't about you, right?
从新泽西回来我就去
I get back from Jersey, I will.
我会的
I will.
你瞧 Cole和我 给她看了疑犯照片
You know, Cole and me, we showed her the spreads.
她指认了Little Man 这个不在话下 但是没有Wee-Bey
Picked out Little Man, no problem. Wouldn't go for Wee-Bey.
于是 我试着敲敲指头
So, I tried the fat finger.
差点跪下求她 让我们的官司能打得顺利点
Damn near down on my knees begging her to make this play easier in court.
你猜她说了什么
You know what she said?
"有时候 我们一定要搏一搏"
"Sometimes things got to play hard."
真警察
Real police.
嗯 是的
Oh, yeah.
- 你它妈的对她干了什么? - 我不知道
- What the fuck did you do to her? - I don't know.
你们两个可是要同乘一辆车
You two in the same car
千里迢迢的到新泽西去
Going to make for a long-ass drive to Jersey.
该死
Shit.
该死的 哥们 这里太"死"了
Damn, man, it's just too still in here.
你知道吗 我们可以...
You know what? We can--
这个地方不错
This place will be fine.
我们唯一要做的 是在这里安个保险箱...
All we really got to do is put a little safe in here someplace...
让他们知道从今以后把钱往这儿送
And let them know the count comes here from now on.
这段时间
Period.
该死的 小子们 你们都改头换面 你们都...
Damn, boy, when y'all change up, y'all--
你们现在那么疑神疑鬼?
Y'all that paranoid?
你从前根本没来过这儿啊
You ain't even been up in there before.
告诉你吧 老姐 现在不同了
I'm telling you, sis, this shit is different.
现在我们不在屋里谈任何事了
We are not going to talk about nothing indoors.
这是新的开始
It's a new day.
现在 伙计们 我们要重新站起来
Thing is, man, we got to get back on our feet.
你们瞧 我是说 我们越是东躲西藏
You know, I mean, the longer we hold off...
维持高楼那片的生意就越难
The harder it's going to be to maintain the towers.
你想东山再起
You want to get it back up,
我和String会全力帮你
You lean to me and String here.
- 不 我还没有完蛋 - 你得避避风头
- No, I ain't down yet. - You need to step back.
她说得没错 兄弟 你不能在这儿再冒一次险
She's right, bro. You can't take a second chance here.
你懂我的意思吗? 在你脱罪之前
You know what I'm saying? Until you fixed,
你姐会帮你打理钱财
Sis going to handle that money...
我会帮你打理货物
I'm going to handle the products.
- 我们一起帮你 - 好吧
- We're here for you. - All right.
但是你去告诉Roberto 让他把东西搞得纯点
But you tell Roberto, he got to make it a serious smoker.
我要公房区那些该死的瘾君子们
I want them motherfucking fiends in the projects....
个个像闻着腥味的苍蝇 你懂吗
I want them dropping like flies. You feel me?
你去告诉他们 让他们知道我们还没完蛋呢
You send out the word, you let them know we ain't dead yet.
- 我的侄子怎么样? - 别操心
- What about my nephew? - Don't fret.
让我和Roberto谈谈
Give me a chance to get with Roberto,
然后我去找Dee
And I'll get up to Dee.
做该做的
Do what needs doing.
告诉他 让他那样受罪我很对不住
Tell him I'm sorry for putting him out there like that.
还有 以后我会补偿他的
And that I'm going to make it up to him.
你是应该补偿他
You going to make it up.
一定要的
Most def.
但是再一次 我要重申 这次的所有合作
But again, I want to make it clear that all of this cooperation
都是基于我的委托人认同的开释条件
Is contingent on a commitment that my client finds acceptable.
否则...
Failing that...
这里说的一切不得公开
Everything said in here, stays in here.
- 同意 - 我相信戴罪立功在Maryland
- Damn straight. - I'm sure a proffer in Maryland
和在Jersey受到的待遇相同 律师
Plays much the same in Jersey, counselor.
而且我也同意 在这宗走私毒品案中
And I do agree that with regard to matters involving drug trafficking,
你的委托人非常配合
Your client has been helpful.
他表示自愿作证 自己是一个中层头目...
He's indicated a willingness to testify that he was a lieutenant...
在Avon Barksdale的贩毒组织里...
In Avon Barksdale's drug distribution organization...
为他舅舅贩卖了大量毒品
Sold large quantities of drugs for his uncle.
参与运钞 参加贩毒组织的会晤 而且...
Delivered money, attended organizational meetings, and...
在此次毒品走私中 代表他的舅舅前往纽约
On one occasion made a trip to New York on the behest of his uncle.
所有这些都和我们已经掌握的事实相符
All of which corroborates much of what we already know.
那还有什么?
What else is there?
谋杀案
The murders.
伙计 为什么你盯着这个不放
Man, why do you keep on that?
我已经告诉你...
I already told you...
那个证人被杀的事我毫不知情
I don't know nothing about that witness being killed.
哪个证人?
Which witness?
记得她吗?
Remember her?
上帝
Jesus.
他们做了她?
They did her?
是啊 跟做了这小子的时间差不多
Yeah, about the same time they did the boy.
都成了孤魂野鬼
All of them bodies.
他们在灭口 伙计
They covering up, man.
是的 我们也是这么想的 不能有任何破绽
Yeah, that's what we think. No loose ends.
这个保安我理解
I can understand the guard.
她收了钱 所以得消失
She got paid, so she had to go.
Orlando 他知道得太多 会告密 所以也得做了他
Orlando, he knew too much, got to snitching, so he had to go.
但是 这孩子...
But then there's the kid...
Wallace
Wallace.
但是今晚我得去Argyle街
But I need to go past Argyle Street tonight.
- 去看看Wallace - Wallace?
- Check in with Wallace. - Wallace?
自从我们帮高楼里的人 找到那个抢劫的小子 他就不混了
He off the hook since we helped the tower crew get that stick-up boy.
我告诉你 Wallace吓死了
I'm telling you, man, Wallace is bugging.
现在几乎连大门都不敢出了
Don't hardly even come out of that room no more.
为什么他会那样
Now, why he be like that?
我想他可能是染上毒瘾了
I'm thinking he might be getting high.
- Wallace? - 这小子有点让我担心
- Wallace? - The boy's scaring me with his shit.
- 好吧 待会儿再聊 - 好的
- All right, holler at me later. - That'll work.
你们全录下了?
You got that shit on tape?
上帝
God!
他的名字是Brandon Wright
His name is Brandon Wright.
炮烙 断指 挖眼 所有的酷刑都用了
Burned him, broke fingers, gouged an eye out, all kinds of fun.
是Wallace发现的他
Wallace was the one who saw.
他看到了这小子
He saw the boy.
但是他真的不知道他们会做什么
But he really didn't think about what they'd do.
你肯定知道
You must have known.
你就站在那个公用电话旁边
You were standing there by that pay phone.
你心里清楚
You knew.
那我能做什么
What was I going to do?
如果我不告诉String 话传到上头
I don't call String, word get back uptown,
到时会怎么样?
What's going to happen then?
所以 你让Wallace等着
So, you told Wallace to wait,
然后你打电话给Stringer 而Stringer
Then you called Stringer and Stringer,
他召集了人马
He gathered the troops.
是的
Yeah.
到了Greek店那儿
And down at the Greek's,
他们让Wallace指认 对吧?
They got Wallace to point the finger, right?
然后他们带着手铐 装成警察进去
Then they went in like cops with handcuffs,
那样就可以慢慢对付Brandon了
So they could take their time on Brandon.
他们在我们能看到的地方 丢下了尸体
They dropped the body where we'd see it.
"杀鸡儆猴" 他们说
"Send a message to the 'jects," they said.
Wallace...
他受不了了
He couldn't handle that.
看到那个之后 他想退出...
After seeing that, he wanted to get out...
回到学校
Go back to school.
我们甚至拿它开玩笑 他都16了 还...
We even joked about it, him being 16 and all...
得像个菜鸟一样 回去从头上初中
Needing to go start back over again as a freshman.
一个星期前 我的舅舅和String 他们把我叫到俱乐部里
About a week ago, my uncle and String, they called me down to the club.
Stringer 他很担心Wallace 我告诉他
Stringer, he's all worried about Wallace, and I told him.
我告诉他 "Wallace不会告密"
I said, "Wallace ain't no snitch."
何况 他妈的他已经不干了
Plus, he's out the fucking game.
我告诉他了
I told him that.
但是其实我得再做点什么
But I needed to do more.
我本应再做点什么...
I should've done more...
但是我没有 该死的 是我害的
But I didn't, and, fuck, that's on me.
能想到是谁杀的Wallace吗?
Any idea who they sent at Wallace?
得了 Dee 好好想想
Come on, Dee, wild guess.
伙计 我真不知道 可能是任何人
Man, I don't know, could've been anybody.
你瞧 杀手很便宜
You know, shooters come cheap.
我不这么想 尤其是在平房区
I don't think so. Not in the Pit.
在他的窝里
Not in his crib.
在那我数到了七张床
I counted seven beds when I was up there.
那些小孩去哪儿了?
Where were the young'uns?
瞧 如果我知道 我会告诉你们
Look, if I knew, I would tell you.
好吧? 我对天发誓 我会告诉你们的
All right? I swear to God, I would tell you.
他们杀害了Orlando  弄伤了一名卧底警探
They've charged with Orlando and the undercover cop...
我们还在追捕中
But we're still hunting.
他...他在费城
Him, he in Philly.
- 你怎么知道? - 我知道是因为我送他去的那儿
- How you know? - I know 'cause I dropped him there.
哪里?
Where?
我不知道 一个角落 最北边 我不知道他现在住哪儿
I don't know, a corner, North end, I don't know where he be staying.
Wee-Bey有没有跟你说过 任何开枪杀人的事?
Did Wee-Bey say anything to you about the shootings?
我们不在车里说事 这是规矩
We don't talk shop in the car. It's a rule we got.
那么 就这样?
So, is that it?
你的委托人必须清楚任何协议
Your client must realize that any agreement...
都是基于他的完全合作
Is dependent on his full cooperation.
没别的了
There ain't nothing else.
Deidre
Deidre.
砰 砰 砰
Tap, tap, tap.
她是我舅舅的马子之一
She was one of my uncle's girls.
但是我们有个证人 把你和她的死联系在一起
But we got people who put you with her the night she's killed.
是的 我不知道他是要去做了她
Yeah, I didn't know that he was going to do her.
我发誓 他们耍了我
I swear. They played me.
怎么耍的?
How so?
我舅舅给我一包3.5克的粉(小包装 八分之一盎司)
My uncle gave me an eight-ball of coke.
让我送去她那儿给她
Told me to take it over there to her.
我很惊讶 因为我以为他已经甩了她
I was surprised, 'cause, you know, I thought he dumped her.
但是他否认了 说不是那回事
But he said, no, it wasn't like that no more.
于是 他让Wee-Bey送我去那儿
So, he had Wee-Bey take me over there.
你瞧 我到了那 敲门之后 她走过来应门
You know, I walked up, knocked on the door, she came to the door,
身上光光的 就披了这件破睡衣
All naked and shit, with this little-ass robe on.
那么 她是你舅舅的马子 却光着身子来开你的门?
So, she's your uncle's girl, but she comes to the door for you naked?
她之前一直这样戏弄对我 伙计
She used to do that shit with me all the time, man.
挑逗 你知道姑娘们怎么做的
Teasing. You know how girls do.
也许你不知道
Maybe you don't.
我不知道
I don't know.
反正 我说
Anyway, I'm like,
"你不打算让我进屋吗?" 她说"不"
"Ain't you going to let me come in?" She says "No,"
因为她得准备迎接 待会儿上门的我的舅舅
Because she got to get ready for my uncle to come by later.
所以 我把粉给了她
So, I give her the coke.
她大笑着要把这玩意儿"冻起来"  等会儿享用
She laughs about how she's going to put that shit on ice, for later on.
放进冰箱
Refrigerate it.
我不知道什么冰箱不冰箱的
I don't know shit about no refrigerator.
我说过了 我没进去
Like I said, I didn't go in.
我转过身 向车子走去...
I turned around, started walking back to the truck...
然后听到了枪声
And I heard this shot.
Wee-Bey 他转身过来 手上拿着他一直喜欢使的点45的大家伙
Wee-Bey, he come running back with this big-ass .45 he liked to use so much.
告诉我说他怎么轻轻敲的窗户
Tells me how he was tapping on the window, real soft.
里面的灯亮着 她不得不走过去...
How with the lights on, she had to walk all the way up...
因为她看不到外面的情况
Because she couldn't see what was on the outside.
然后等她走到那里 看向窗外
And when she gets up to the window and looks out....
你做得很好 D'Angelo
You did good, D'Angelo.
是的 确实
Yeah, you did.
你们都不明白 伙计
Y'all don't understand, man.
你们都不明白
Y'all don't get it.
你在这环境里长大
You grow up in this shit.
我祖父是Butch Stamford
My grandfather was Butch Stamford.
你们知道这个Butch Stamford是谁吗?
You know who Butch Stamford was in this town?
我的所有家人
All my people, man,
我父亲 我舅舅 我的兄弟姐妹...
My father, my uncles, my cousins...
我们都是干这行的
It's just what we do.
你只能忍受着这一切
You just live with this shit...
直到你感到喘不过气来
Until you can't breathe no more.
我对天发誓...
I swear to God,
我在拘留所呆了八个月...
I was courtside for eight months...
在牢里我更自由
And I was freer in jail
比我在家里的时候
Than I was at home.
你有什么打算?
What are you looking for?
我想要脱身
I want it to go away.
- 我不能... - 我想要Wallace想要过的
- I can't-- - I want what Wallace wanted.
我想重新开始
I want to start over.
这是我想要的 我不在乎在哪儿
That's what I want. I don't care where.
随便哪里 我不在乎
Anywhere. I don't give a fuck.
我只想去一个地方 能让我像个正常人一样活着
I just want to go somewhere where I can breathe like regular folk.
你们要是能满足我...
You give me that...
我就给你们他们
And I'll give you them.
不 很棒 真的很棒
No, that's great. Really great.
嗯
Yeah.
我们就这么做
That's our move.
好的
Okay.
今天有了大进展 很大的进展
We broke it open tonight. Wide open.
我会把这案子做得轰轰烈烈
I'm bringing this case in big.
那算是报了Burrell的一箭之仇 是吗?
So, this squares things with Burrell, right?
祝他早日升天
To hell with the man.
但是我觉得我们掌握的资料 足够找上联邦调查局
But I think we might have enough to reach out to the feds...
试试看和他们的合作
Try to run this thing through them.
Cedric
Cedric.
他知道钱的事 Marla
He knows about the money, Marla.
他很早之前就知道了
He's known for a long while.
事实上 这样我就不奇怪 他会选我办这件案子了
Fact is, I wouldn't be surprised if it's why he picked me for this case.
他有没有...
What does he...
- 你打算... - 如果他想动我 他早就动手了
- What are you going to-- - He's got me if he wants me.
事实上 我觉得他不想动我
Thing is, I don't think he wants me.
风险太大
Too much at stake.
乱子太多
Too much mess.
就像这案子
Kind of like this case.
我得承认 Jimmy 这是宗大案子
I have to admit it, Jimmy, this is a great case.
不只是因为Greggs 不只是因为它牵涉到的方方面面
Not just because of Greggs, because it goes to that and answers that...
而是因为它可以挖得那么深
But because of how deep it goes.
我是说 谋杀 金钱...
I mean, the murders, the money--
老天爷 从那个小子开口说话起 我就觉得自己像喝醉了一样
Jesus, I feel like I've been drunk ever since that kid started talking to us.
你还能开车吧?
You okay to drive?
我可以送你回家 明天你再来取车
I can drop you home. You can pick up your car tomorrow.
不 我很好 我好极了 这他妈的爽极了
No, I'm good. I'm great, this was fucking great!
你想让联邦调查局介入?
You want to try to go federal with this?
助理美国检察官 可以代表美国政府在刑事诉讼中诉讼
我一定加入 我同时也是任助理美国检察官
I am up for it. I get cross-designated as an AUSA,
我们可以大干一场 你知道吧
And we can really run with it, you know?
可以写进职业生涯的大案子
Career fucking case.
反正...
Anyway....
Ronnie 发生在...
Ronnie, the thing at...
去Levy那的那天 我有点...
Levy's the other day, I was....
我有点...
I was--
天啊 Ronnie 不能在这儿 你在干嘛
Jesus, Ronnie, not here. What are you doing?
说得你好像从没在总部的 停车库里干过似的
Like you never did it in the headquarters garage before?
圣父 圣母 圣子啊
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
看看谁大摇大摆自己冲进来了
Look what just walked in without a fucking escort.
城里的Roy Brown 活着的传奇...
Downtown Roy Brown, the living legend...
在他自己的脑子里
In his own mind.
城外的Lester Freamon
Uptown Lester Freamon.
我操 有多久了?
Fuck me, how long's it been?
你的退休派对 对吧?
Your retirement party, wasn't it?
这就是退休吗
And this is retirement?
是啊 多漂亮的地方
Yeah. Nice fucking digs?
我问过我的领导 什么时候能给我点阳光
I asked my supervisor when I'll see a little sunlight.
狗娘养的矮冬瓜说 "等你的小组能赚钱了"
Runt cocksucker says, "When your unit turns a profit."
但是我已经满足了
But enough of my joy.
你们需要什么?
What do you guys need?
我们需要一份通信记录 但不是在Maryland
We need a trap and trace, but not in Maryland.
宾夕法尼亚 费城
Pennsylvania, Philly.
那你得去找他们
You got to go through them.
我们试过了 浪费了一个星期 结果告诉我们不行
We try that, we lose a week, they tell us it can't be done...
接着又得花一个星期去搞传票
Then another week to okay our subpoena.
这比单纯的追踪要复杂一点
It's a little more complicated than just a straight-up trace.
我们需要一张费城的电话清单
We actually need a list of phones in Philly
只要在过去的星期里打过这个电话
That called this number in the past week.
这是谁的号码?
What's the number?
毒贩的律师 城里办公室(Levy的办公室)的电话
Drug lawyer, downtown office.
觉得应该来开账单(电话公司)的地方查
Thought Billing would be the place to look.
如果我们可以 我没有说可以哦
If we can do it, and I'm not saying we can...
也要它妈的一个星期 也许是两周
It's going to be a fucking week, maybe two.
谢谢 Roy
Thanks, Roy.
Lester 难道你不该接下去说
Lester, isn't this supposed to be the time...
这玩意儿它妈的有多重要吗
You tell me how all-fired fucking important this is?
这个费城的电话
The Philly number
能帮我们抓住开枪 打了一名女卧底警员的混蛋
Gives us the mope who shot that female undercover.
我告诉你 Fitz 这是宗完美的案子
I'm telling you, Fitz, it's the perfect case.
- 你会喜欢的 - 听上去不错
- You'll love it. - It sounds great.
但是正如我说过的 我们不再搞什么毒品案了
But like I said, Jimmy, we're not fishing for drug cases anymore.
试试药管局吧
Try DEA.
不 他们的办公室 离我们重案组的太近了
No, that field office is too close to our CID.
我们要是过去 我们的头儿能在定下会议前就知道
We go there, our bosses know it before a meeting is scheduled.
你们的头儿不知道你们在搞这个?
Your bosses don't know you're doing this?
那么谁会来?
Who'll be coming?
我 一个叫Freamon的探员 还有Daniels
Me, a detective name of Freamon, and Daniels.
我可以为Daniels担保 哥们
I can speak for Daniels, brother.
这案子他是全力以赴的
He's played this thing out with real heart.
拜托 给我们安排一下吧
Come on, set something up.
好的
All right.
能给我复印10份吗
Could I get 10 copies?
- 10份? - 10份 是的
- 10 copies? - 10, right.
没问题吧
No problems?
没
No.
没?
No?
好的 先生 欢迎再光临
All right, man, I'll get at you.
你把门锁了 是吧?
You locked that door, right?
嗯 好了 听好了
Yeah? All right, so listen.
这玩意儿还不能马上卖 明白吗?
It's not street-ready, all right?
所以 大家要自己管好自己那份 要分装
So, everybody got to work on their own cut and vial up.
现在 听我说 让他们搞清楚了
Now, listen to me, tell them to get this straight.
三份这个 明白吗?
Three parts of this, all right?
一份原料 明白吗?
To one of raw, all right?
在找到新的作坊之前 我们就这么干
And that's how we gonna do until we get the new stash.
还有 我要你把话放出去
And I want you to put the word out there
我们回来了
That we're back up.
明白吗?
Understand me?
我们回来了
We're back up.
不错的目标
It's a good target.
你们有一桩厉害的案子
You guys have a pretty good case here.
单单看里面的暴力犯罪
Look at the violence alone.
起码有十几桩谋杀案 包括一名出庭证人
There's at least a dozen murders, including state's witnesses.
如果你能帮我们把这个Barksdale的侄子
If you can help us squeeze the Barksdale kid
弄进证人保护计划 我们可以大干一场
Into a witness protection program we can run wild with this thing.
但是没有供货商
No suppliers though.
我们还在继续深入调查
We're still looking for a way into that.
监听线上还没有 能和纽约联系在一起的线索
There was nothing on the wire that took us toward New York.
问题是
The trouble is,
我们有个后911时期的纲领
We have these post-9l1 protocols.
我们不能立新的缉毒案
We can't pick up any new narcotics work...
除非它涉及大规模的组织犯罪
Unless it goes to priority organized-crime targets.
这意味着要么是意大利黑手党 或者是哥伦比亚人
Meaning Cosa Nostra or Colombians.
也许是俄国人
Or Russians maybe.
我们在Baltimore没有什么哥伦比亚人
We don't have any Colombians in Baltimore.
我们也没有什么古惑仔
We don't have any wise guys.
我们只有一群地头蛇 忙着把西区搞得天翻地覆
All we got is a whole lot of locals a little busy tearing the Westside apart.
我明白你的话 但这是整个调查局的规定
I hear you, but the Bureau-wide protocol applies.
要和你们合作 我们就得有一个犯罪集团为目标
To run with you on this, we need a recognized OC target...
或者更好是报复性恐怖主义 或者腐败
Or, even better, a connect to counterterrorism or corruption.
你们有那样的线索...
You go near stuff like that...
这样我们就可以向ASAC(特工助理主管)说说
We have something we can bring to our ASAC.
什么样的腐败?
What kind of corruption?
不知道 你有什么?
Don't know. What kind you got?
Poot 我们能开业了没?
Poot, we up yet?
- Roc-Roc和东西在哪儿呢? - 在打包呢
- Where Roc-Roc at with the shit? - Package in.
那是谁?
Who is it?
- Onion和他的小瘪三 - Onion?
- Onion and them off-brand niggers. - Onion?
- 他们有什么烂货? - 他们管它叫"黄盖"(黄色盖子)
- What the fuck they got? - Some shit they call yellow tops.
"黄盖"?
Yellow tops?
这有黄盖 嘿 黄盖
Got them yellow tops, y'all, yellow tops.
黄盖  黄盖 这有黄盖
Yellows tops. Got them yellow tops.
狗娘养的 造反啊?
Motherfucker, what the fuck is up?
他妈的干什么呢?!
Fuck is y'all doing?
你想咋样随意 但是后果自负
Do what you feel. But be ready to finish what you start.
你们干嘛呢? 这又不是自由市场 你们知道的
What you doing? This ain't no open market, you know that.
屁个市场 小子 你们有个屁卖啊!
Ain't no market at all, nigger. You ain't got shit to sell.
还是乖乖滚一边去吧
Back that ass up for those that do.
- 你知道吗 - 什么
- You know what? - What?
操你妈 它妈的滚回去 贱人!
Fuck you. Get the fuck out of here, bitch!
瞧 这就是我们赢不了的原因
See, that's why we can't win.
为什么不行?
Why not?
他们搞砸了 吃顿海扁
They fuck up, they get beat.
我们搞砸了 去领养老金
We fuck up, they give us pensions.
收起来! 它妈的滚出这儿!
Close it! Get the fuck out of here!
听说你这个目击证人当得不怎么样
Heard you ain't much as an eyeball witness.
水平和老百姓一样差劲
Bad as any civilian.
我猜是吧
Guess so.
我们到哪儿了?
Where we at?
什么?
With what?
当然是案子 笨蛋
With the case, fool.
天啊 休息一下吧
Jesus, give it a rest.
现在谁在监听?
What's on the wire?
- 拜托 - 那个已经断了
- Come on, man. - Wire's dead.
我们突袭他们的老窝后 就全变了
They changed up after we hit them with raids.
Daniels没有告诉你?
Daniels didn't tell you?
该死的 没有
Hell, no.
他只告诉我好的消息
He only talks to me about the good shit.
关于你们怎么追查我的凶手之类的
About how y'all were onto my shooters and stuff.
是啊 我们是没了窃听线
Yeah, well, we lost the wire,
但是好消息是 D'Angelo投诚了
But the good news is D'Angelo's flipped...
我们联系上了联邦调查局 也许可以...
And we're talking to the feds about maybe--
你们都去死吧
Fuck both y'all.
她希望我退出
She wants me to quit.
说没有什么值得我这样
Says there ain't nothing worth this.
于是 我答应她会考虑一下
So, I promised her I'd think about it.
你会说什么?
What do you say?
我不知道
I don't know.
我猜...
I guess--
你做你自己觉得该做的吧
You should do what you need to.
但她是对的
But she's right.
不值得
It isn't worth it.
不值吗?
No?
是的 大概是吧
Yeah. Probably not.
不论如何 你怎么过了那么久才来?
Anyway, what took you so long getting up in here?
该死的 没有慰问卡片 也没有鲜花
Shit, no cards, no flowers.
我是说 你搞什么啊 Jimmy?
I mean, what the fuck, Jimmy?
我没法...我...
I couldn't, l...
我觉得...
I felt....
像这样的案子 总会有像你或是Sydnor...
A case like this, it's always you or Sydnor...
或是其他黑人警察会去当卧底
Or some other black cop who ends up going undercover.
我发誓 如果我能重新来过...
I swear, if I could do it over....
如果我...
If l....
如果我能重新来过...
If I could do it over...
你知道我会怎么做吗?
You know what I'd do?
在那该死的枪上多贴几层胶带
Put more tape on that fucking gun.
对不起 Kima
I'm sorry, Kima.
对不起
I'm sorry.
反正...
Anyway,
既然你来到这里 在我面前求饶什么的
Since I got you up in here acting like my bitch and shit...
带着你悔恨的泪水 这些有的没的
With all your guilty-ass crying and whatnot...
也许你能为我做点什么
Maybe you can do something for me.
她说你干得不错
She said you were doing good.
说她为你骄傲
Said she was proud of you.
她怎么样了?
How's she doing?
还是有点受惊
Still shook.
但是她想让你收下这个...
But she wanted you to have that...
让我告诉你 她很抱歉送晚了
And told me to tell you she's sorry to be late with it.
她就是心肠好 是吧
Girl got such heart, you know?
是啊
Yeah.
这些就够我用的了 伙计
This is enough for what I got going now, man.
你把剩下的还给她
You give the rest back to her.
你确定?
Are you sure?
替我问她好
Give her my love.
行
Right.
McNulty
McNulty.
别告诉她
Don't tell her.
- 有什么 伙计? - 去那边 哥们
- What you got, man? - Over there, man.
真它妈的见鬼了
Un-fucking-believable.
五个家伙挤掉了我 不仅是你
Five guys got jumped. Not just you.
还有四个家伙跑到我前面去了
Four other guys jumped me.
抱歉 伙计
I'm sorry, man.
一定是那些野蛮执法的投诉...
It's got to be all the brutality complaints...
这意味着跟我成绩的好坏 他妈的没一点关系
Which means it ain't never gonna matter how well I do on no fucking test.
这可说不好 也许你在下一批的名单里呢
You don't know that. You might make the next list, you know?
这说不准的
You don't know.
我猜自己不是领导的料
Guess I ain't leadership material.
- 恭喜你 Carv - 谢谢
- Congratulations, Carv. - Thanks.
喂?
Yeah?
现在是狗屁世道
The world is on its ass.
电话公司的人打电话找你
Guy called for you from the phone company.
说他找到了你想在费城找的电话
Says he's got the number you wanted for a house in Philadelphia.
好极了 谢谢
Beautiful, thank you.
案子办得漂亮
Good casework.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想就算告诉你们也不算泄密了 在座的Arnold
I don't think I'm giving anything away by telling that Arnold here
手上份有针对Davis参议员 取证了两年半的调查
Has had a file on Senator Davis for two and a half years.
我们查了很久才有所发现
It took us a while to see it,
但是猫腻都在这儿 在这个西区重建计划里
But the quid pro quo is right there in that Westside redevelopment mess.
Barksdale 或者是他的幌子 贿赂足够多的城里的政客
Barksdale, or his fronts, grease enough city politicians...
把未来开发区的样子
And word comes back years in advance
从他们嘴里先打听出来
Where the development zone's going to be.
然后他买下所有的垃圾地产
He buys up every piece of garbage real estate he can...
炒卖个三四次 抬高它的价格
Flips it three or four times, exaggerating the values.
而政府会付给他上百万...
The city's gonna pay him millions...
为了重建计划而收回这些地产
To condemn the properties for the renewal project.
有很多工作要做 但是我们愿意
It's a lot to work with, but we're willing.
问题是...
The question is,
你们的合作人能为我们指证参议员
Can your cooperator give us the senator...
或者别的政治人物吗?
Or any other political figure?
合作人?
The cooperator?
D'Angelo Barksdale
D'Angelo Barksdale.
在金钱犯罪上 他有什么能告诉我们的?
What does he have for us on the money?
什么都没有
Nothing.
他能帮你们查毒品 查暴力犯罪
He gives you the drugs and the violence.
他能给你们Avon Barksdale Stringer Bell
He gives you Avon Barksdale, Stringer Bell.
而他们能给我们参议员
And they give us the senator.
也许可以
Maybe, yeah.
你是说要让Barksdale和Bell成为合作者
You're talking about turning Barksdale and Bell into cooperators...
好让政客成为主要打击目标?
And making the politicians the primary target?
当然了
Of course.
不 去它妈的政客 这是关于Barksdale和Bell
No, fuck the politicians. It's Barksdale and Bell.
是这些家伙让西Baltimore 变成了自由交战区
Those guys have turned West Baltimore into a free-fire zone.
没人说他们能逍遥法外
No one's saying they walk.
你们说的是 如果我们给了你们这案子
What you are saying is that if we bring you the case...
你们就打算给Barksdale和Bell任意地减刑
It's your intention to let Barksdale and Bell reduce
只要他们愿意合作的话?
Any sentence they get through cooperation?
我的上帝啊 你们是认真的吗?
Jesus Christ, are you kidding?
你们都看到了这些家伙的案底
You're seeing all this ass-backwards.
探员 我们在这里是想采取一次 针对政治贿赂案的调查
Detective, in this office we have a mandate to pursue political corruption.
你能相信这些家伙吗?
Can you believe these guys?
- Jimmy 瞧 - 什么
- Jimmy, look. - What?
毒品和杀人不再重要了?
Drugs and murder don't cut it anymore?
那恐怖主义呢?
How about terrorism?
这些家伙已经杀了14...15个人
These guys have dropped 14, 15 bodies.
那些证人 合作人...
The witnesses, cooperators--
你的这种夸大其词没有用了 探员
That kind of hyperbole doesn't serve anyone, detective.
我想我们在此案上的意见并不一致
I think we're going with a different direction on this.
谢谢你们的时间
Thank you for your time.
西Baltimore正在衰亡 而你们这些吃干饭的
West Baltimore is dying, and you empty suits...
却只顾上蹿下跳  忙着对一帮政客开火
Are running around trying to pin some politician's pelt to the wall.
还以为你是真警察呢 兄弟
Thought you was real police, brother.
看来 他们把你弄到了这里
So, they got you all the way out here?
我开始还以为你在新泽西
I started out thinking you was in Jersey.
结果 你没在新泽西
You ain't in Jersey.
我想他们把你关在市拘留所里了吧
I figured they still got you down in Central Booking.
但是 却是在这里...
But, all the way out here....
你的意思很清楚了
Do send a message, though.
是的 有些人该明白了
Yeah, a message needs sending.
你是怎么找到我的
How y'all even find me?
没人能阻止一个母亲 找到自己的孩子 不是吗
Ain't no one going to keep a mother from her son, right?
你瞧 他一直说家族
You know, he's always talking family.
"家族至上" 是他常说的
"Family is the heart," he say.
那么 我也是家人
Well, I'm family...
对吧?
Ain't l?
能不能把我当回事?
What about me for once?
这不对
It ain't right.
什么才对?
What's right?
你想让他站出来
You like for him to step up,
背下一切 让你离开?
Take all the weight, and let you walk?
因为他会的 你知道他会
Because he will. You know he will.
但如果他进去了...
But if he got to go away...
就意味着你得站出来 替他的位置
That mean you got to step up and fill his shoes.
你准备好了吗?
You ready for that?
妈妈 你知道我没有
Ma, you know I ain't.
我没有准备好 我永远也不会准备好
I ain't ready, and I'm never gonna be ready for this game.
- Dee 拜托 - 瞧
- Dee, come on. - Look.
他们给了我一个离开的机会
They're giving me a chance to walk away...
到另一个地方重新开始
To start again someplace else.
那你给了他们什么
And what you giving them?
瞧...
Look....
他搞砸了 Dee 他清楚
He messed up, Dee, he knows it.
现在如果你想报复他 你可以
Now if you want to get even with him, you can.
但如果你伤害了他 就是伤害了整个家族
But if you hurt him, you hurt this whole family.
我们所有人 我 Trina 还有其他兄弟
All of us. Me and Trina and the cousins.
还有Donette 你的孩子
And Donette, too. And your baby.
你的亲儿子
Your own baby boy.
这都是游戏的一部分 Dee
This right here is part of the game, Dee.
没有了这游戏...
And without the game...
整个家庭都会滚到 该死的公租房里喝西北风
This whole family would be down in the fucking Terrace Iiving off scraps.
该死的 那时候家都不成家了
Shit, we probably wouldn't even be a family.
重新开始?
Start over?
如果连亲人都不在了 还谈什么重新开始?
How the fuck you going to start over without your peoples?
甚至留不住自己的儿子?
Without your own child, even?
如果你在这世上没了家
If you ain't got family in this world...
你它妈的还能有什么?
What the hell you got?
要是这个狗娘养的Wee-Bey反抗 那就省得打官司了
This motherfucker Wee-Bey twitches, there won't even be a trial.
Carver探员 说句话
Detective Carver, a word?
关上门
Shut the door.
什么事 队长?
What's up, Lieutenant?
你有什么要对我说的吗?
Anything you want to tell me?
已经几个星期了...
Been weeks now...
副局几乎每次都在我知道之前 就知道了组里发生的事
The Deputy Ops knows what's going on in this unit almost before I do.
除了上个星期
Except last week...
我们在Barksdale的俱乐部里装窃听器
We run the bug up into Barksdale's club office...
只有这一次 Burrell没有跳出来
And Burrell, for once, he's a step behind.
你瞧
You see it?
- 也许他... - 我都明白
- Maybe he-- - I see it.
我看看办公室里的人
I look around the office...
我发现我的人里有一个去做在职培训了
And I see that one of my people is at the academy for in-service.
队长 我发誓 这不是我的主意
Lieutenant, I swear, it wasn't my idea.
我是想做自己的本分 干好自己的活儿...
I'm minding my business, doing my fucking job...
而他打电话过来请我喝咖啡 吃点心
When the man calls me for coffee and a Danish.
我是说 我它妈的还没上过 这大楼的八层呢
I mean, I never even been on the eighth floor of that fucking building.
而这个该死的副局长告诉我
And there's the Deputy fucking Ops telling me
他有多关心这案子
How concerned he is about the case...
他多么需要知道进展
How he needs to be informed.
我是说 他它妈的是个副局长
I mean, he's the Deputy fucking Ops, man.
几周以后...
Couple weeks from now...
你会调到某个辖区
You're gonna be in some district somewhere...
那里会有11到12名制服警员 看着你的一举一动
With 11 or 12 uniforms looking to you for everything.
他们之中有一些会成为好警察
And some of them are going to be good police.
有一些会显得年轻而无知
Some of them are going to be young and stupid.
还有少数的一些 会变成坏蛋
A few are going to be pieces of shit.
但所有人都会拿你当榜样
But all of them will take their cue from you.
你表现出忠诚 他们会学到忠诚
You show loyalty, they learn loyalty.
你表现出工作至上 他们会看重工作
You show them it's about the work, it'll be about the work.
你给他们看到其他把戏
You show them some other kind of game,
他们以后也会玩相同的把戏
Then that's the game they'll play.
我从东区来...
I came on in the Eastern...
那里 有个一无是处的警督想当警监
And there was a piece-of-shit lieutenant hoping to be a captain...
一些该死的混蛋警司想当警督
Piece-of-shit sergeants hoping to be lieutenants.
巡警属地方自建民防 非同一编制
很快 一些他妈的狗屁巡警 也想给自己谋个一官半职
Pretty soon we had piece-of-shit patrolmen trying to figure the job for themselves.
那时发生的那些事情
And some of what happens then
他妈的让人不堪回首
Is hard as hell to live down.
总有一天 你得做出决定
Comes a day you're going to have to decide
是选自己 还是选工作
Whether it's about you or about the work.
大陪审团周二开庭
Grand jury came in Tuesday.
不过你已经知道了 对吧
But you knew that, right?
今天我们在申请飞行许可(指跨境追捕)
We're working a flight warrant today.
这里还有很多事要做 在办公室里
There's a lot to do here, in-office.
但是我会对那玩意留个心
I'd be careful with that, though.
我明白 这玩意的扳机是有点松
I understand the trigger pull used to be light.
压住他 压住他
Keep him down, keep him down.
抓住他了? 让他起来 让他起来
You got him? Get him up there, get him up.
一群不要脸的杂种
Bunch of low-bottom bitches.
铐住他
Get his wrists.
你们它妈的怎么可以乱动我的车
Y'all didn't have to fuck with my ride.
混蛋们走狗屎运了
Motherfuckers got lucky.
喂?
Yeah?
Denton的乡下律师让警卫不好过了
Podunk lawyer in Denton's giving the guards a hard time...
纠结把D'Angelo 从初审法院转移到那儿的问题
About moving D'Angelo from original jurisdiction.
把电话接过来
Put the call through.
好的
Okay.
Mace警官 我是Pearlman检察官
Officer Mace, ASA Pearlman,
你对律师有意见?
You got a problem with the lawyer?
好的 让这混蛋说话
Okay, put the asshole on.
他来了
This is he.
你没有把事情简单化 Jimmy
You do not make it easy, Jimmy.
我得承认 此刻我非常矛盾
I have to admit, I am deeply ambivalent.
抱歉?
Excuse me?
坐! 坐啊!
Sit. Sit!
给您
Here.
我从Bunk那听说了
I heard from Bunk.
费城 漂亮的一仗
Philly. Great work.
你们都干得漂亮
You all did great work.
从我现在看到的破案率看...
And the number of clearances I'm looking at here...
老天 这还是今年第一次
Christ, for the first time this year,
我们的破案率超过了40%
We got the clearance rate up over 40%.
这是一方面
That's on the one hand.
另一方面 我知道副局长
On the other hand, I know the Deputy Ops
今天早上接到了联邦第一副检察长的电话
Got a call from the first deputy U.S. Attorney this morning...
询问有没有像你这样的混蛋 真的在为我们工作
Asking whether an asshole such as yourself really works for us.
当然 这是局长第一次听说居然有手下
Of course, this is the first the Deputy hears his troops...
想瞒着他把案子转给联邦调查局
Are creeping behind his back to take a case federal...
可之前明明是说案子已经结了
When they've already been told the case is closed.
你是个好探员
You're a good detective.
我得承认 你身上有一股勇气
And I've got to admit you got some stones on you.
你是不是真的说第一副检察长 是吃干饭的?
Did you actually call the first deputy an empty suit?
我希望你能有个好归宿 Jimmy
I want to see you land okay, Jimmy.
那么 告诉我 你不想去哪儿?
So, tell me, where don't you want to go?
你们和我一样清楚Baltimore市的陪审员
You all know that Baltimore city jurors
几乎是无所不能的
Are capable of just about anything.
瞧 如果你们想干坐在这几个月
Now, look, you want to sit around for months on end...
听完这一大堆对话断断续续的电话录音
Going through a bunch of half-heard half-said telephone conversations...
来展示你们的侦查成果
and see how well you do...
我绝对尊重你们的付出
I'll certainly respect the effort.
那不只是监听到的对话
It's not just talk on the wire.
我们查获了大量钱物和一大堆毒品
We've got seized money and lot of dope on the table.
还有多起暴力犯罪
And a lot of violence.
所有这些都和Barksdale先生无关
All of which stops way short of Mr. Barksdale.
你们都知道
You know this.
除了新泽西的抓捕
All of it except for the New Jersey bust.
这个他得认
That one he eats.
也许吧
Maybe he does.
也许他会承认其中一条持有未遂的罪名
Maybe he pleads to one count of attempted possession...
然后接受 我不知道 也许三到四年的刑期
And takes, I don't know, maybe three, four.
也许他能让你们录音里的所有人
Maybe he can arrange for everyone you have...
也跟着一起认罪
On those tapes to follow suit.
也许你们能给那些没有前科的定个5年刑期
Maybe you get five-year pleas from those with no prior felony convictions...
有一次前科的10年 两次以上的15年
10 years for those with one prior, 15 for two or more.
那么 那些谋杀呢?
What about the murders?
也许我们承认你们已经抓到的Brice先生
Maybe we acknowledge you've got Mr. Brice cold for...
将承担谋杀Orlando Blocker和袭警的罪名
Murder of Orlando Blocker and wounding of the police officer.
谁?
Who?
Wee-Bey
Wee-Bey.
作为Brice的代理人
Representing Mr. Brice...
我非常肯定 为了避免被判死刑
I'm fairly confident that to avoid the death penalty...
他会愿意交代至少
He'll proffer to at least
六起你们尚未破获的谋杀案
A half dozen of your open murders.
会招出其他同伙吗?
Naming co-conspirators?
如果愿意配合 我会愿意考虑有期徒刑
For that kind of cooperation, I'd be willing to consider straight life.
不 谢谢 我相信Brice先生
No, indeed. I believe Mr. Brice is
愿意独自承担他所有的犯罪事实
Ready to take sole responsibility for all of his crimes.
不过 你们还是能结掉起码六起案件
Still, you walk away with at least a half-dozen clearances.
资产
Assets.
你们可以没收脱衣舞俱乐部
You take the strip club,
你们也可以没收任何和毒品运输有关的车辆
You take whatever trucks and cars you can link to the drug trafficking,
当然还有你们搜到的现金
And also whatever cash you've seized.
他还有一大堆别的资产
He's got dozens of other properties:
殡葬馆 拖车公司
The funeral parlor, the towing company.
不 不 你们可以没收汽车
No. You get the cars,
因为你们可以把它 和非法活动联系在一起
Because you can tie them to illegal activity.
但是其他财产 你们无权没收
But there's nothing else of his to take.
那么 你们保住了大部分的财产 大部分的不动产
So, you keep most of the money, most of the real estate...
而Stringer Bell还在逍遥法外  操纵着一切
And Stringer Bell stays on the street with his hand on the throttle.
如果你们有针对Bell先生的指控  那就请上诉吧
If you have a charge against Mr. Bell, file it.
否则 我只能认为
Otherwise, I understand
那些数小时长的录音里 没有任何涉及他的证据
That nothing in all those hours of tape implicates him.
三年或四年还不够 Maury
Three or four years ain't enough, Maury.
对Avon Barksdale来说不够
Not for Avon Barksdale.
不够?
No?
那就开个条件吧
Make an offer.
Baltimore市巡回法庭第14号庭开庭
Part 14 of the circuit court of Baltimore City now in session.
- 请就座 - 首先
- Be seated. - First up.
州政府控告Avon Randolph  Barksdale 法官大人
State versus Avon Randolph Barksdale, Your Honor.
罪名 持有并企图贩卖
One count of possession with intent to distribute...
非法毒品 一公斤海洛因
To wit, a kilogram of heroin.
- 你有事实陈述吗? - 是的 法官大人
- You have a statement of facts? - Yes, Your Honor.
Barksdale愿意承认上诉罪名
Mr. Barksdale is offering a plea of guilty...
以换取在劳教所最高7年的刑罚
In exchange for a maximum of seven years in DOC...
以上均基于以下被认可的犯罪事实:
In consideration of the following agreed-upon facts:
大约在2002年9月17日
On or about the date of September 17, 2002...
在新泽西Essex郡辖区内
In the jurisdiction of Essex County, New Jersey...
Newark分局的Robert Warren巡警
Trooper Robert Warren of the Newark barracks...
对一辆租用的福特金牛执行了交通拦截
Effected a traffic stop on a rented Ford Taurus...
此车正向南行驶到13号出口附近
Traveling southbound near Exit 13.
此次交通拦截 是由于得到了一条信息
That traffic stop resulted from information gleaned...
这个信息 是在监听Barksdale先生
From electronic surveillance of Mr. Barksdale
和他的侄子D'Angelo Barksdale的时候
And his nephew, D'Angelo Barksdale...
由专案组警员使用电子设备
By detectives assigned to a special detail...
在缉毒组高级警员带领下 监听到的
Under the command of a city narcotics supervisor.
搜查这辆从BWI机场AVIS租车点 租来的轿车后
A search of the vehicle, rented from the Avis location at B.W.I. Airport...
发现了一公斤高纯度海洛因
Revealed that a kilogram of nearly pure heroin...
被隐藏在轿车的备用轮胎内
Was concealed beneath the spare tire in the car trunk.
在认罪协议中 Barksdale先生 承认他涉嫌购买
In accepting this plea, Mr. Barksdale acknowledges his role in procuring...
那些被缴获的毒品 并企图稀释
Those drugs with the intent to dilute,
包装后出售这些数量的海洛因
Package, and sell retail amounts of heroin....
Deidre Kresson Roland Leggett...Toreen Boyd
Deidre Kresson, Roland Leggett, Toreen Boyd,
都死于同一把枪
All tied to the same gun.
而且 我们还有那两个抢劫的小子
Plus, we got the stick-up boys,
Brandon Wright...John Bailey
Brandon Wright, John Bailey.
算上Orlando 总共六个
With Orlando, that makes six.
加上谋杀警察未遂
Plus the attempted murder on a police.
就这样?
That it?
如果我再说一桩 会不会更好?
I do better if I give them more?
无期徒刑 不得假释 就是字面上的意思
Life, no parole, means what it says.
协助调查能让你免予死刑 没有别的
This proffer keeps you off death row. That's all it does.
你让一个警察吃了子弹 Brice先生
You were on the wrong side of a cop getting shot, Mr. Brice.
如果你还异想天开 想从累累罪行中得到有期徒刑
You want to dream about straight life for these bodies...
你就得放聪明点 交代Avon Barksdale和Stringer Bell
You got to wake up talking about Avon Barksdale and Stringer Bell.
不
No.
但是谋杀案 你最好把有的都交代了
But for murders, you might as well give them what you have...
因为任何未交代的案子 都将不受此次协议的影响
Because anything you leave out is outside the deal.
如果日后被他们发现 他们还是能告你
If they learn about it later, they can charge you later.
那就到时候再说吧
Fuck it then.
为了再吃份自家的三明治和土豆沙拉
For another pit sandwich and some potato salad...
我愿意再说点
I'll go a few more.
- 你想要哪种? - 五分熟 多放些辣根
- How you want that? - Medium rare, a lot of horseradish.
好吧 我做了Little Man
All right, I did Little Man...
觉得警察这事上他会成软脚蟹
Thinking he might get weak on that cop getting shot.
是吗 尸体在哪儿?
Yeah? Where's the body?
Druid山公园 爬虫馆后面
Druid Hill. Behind the reptile house.
在长草之前 也许你还能看到点剩下的尸体
You get back in them weeds, you might could find what's left of him.
好吧 这是第七个 还有什么?
All right, that's seven. What else you got?
说说证人如何?
How about them witnesses?
那个女保安 还有那个叫什么来着的
The security lady, and what's his name,
那个维修工人?
The maintenance man?
Gant?
是的 Gant
Yeah, Gant.
你一个人杀了Gant?
You did Gant alone?
他们的土豆沙拉卖完了 要卷心菜沙拉吗
They're out of potato salad. How about slaw?
从电子监听中得到的信息
Information gleaned from electronic surveillance...
显示Watkins先生 又名Ronnie Moe
Would also show that Mr. Watkins, a.k.a. Ronnie Moe...
全程参与了在高楼区海洛因和可卡因的贩卖
Was integrally involved in the distribution of heroin and cocaine in the high-rises...
Fayette 734号和北Fremont 221号
At 734 Fayette and 221 North Fremont.
他愿意承认共谋罪 以换取
In exchange for his pleading guilty to one count of conspiracy...
在劳教所不超过15年的刑罚
He agrees to a sentence not to exceed 15 years in DOC.
Watkins先生 已经在2001年Prevas法官的法庭上
Mr. Watkins, who is on probation for a drug distribution charge...
被判非法贩毒罪 并处于缓行期间...
That was adjudicated in judge Prevas' court in August, 2001 ....
Cedric!
Cantrell警长
Major Cantrell.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢
- Congrats. - Thanks.
- 那么 他们要把你派去哪里? - 西北片 Spurgeon退休了
- So, where they sending you? - Northwest. Spurgeon's retiring.
我听说过这件事情
I heard that was going to happen.
如果想换个地方 尽管开口
Ever feel like a change, give a yell.
我挺想找个尽职的警督
I could use a good shift lieutenant.
我是说 眼下 那儿乱成了一锅粥
I mean, right now, the whole fucking district's a mess.
哪里不是呢?
What isn't?
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Good seeing you. - You, too.
你瞧 这不是药管局 一点都不像
You see, this ain't no DEU. It ain't like that.
你们一来到这儿 工作就变了
When you all came downtown, the job changed.
在这里 我们办大案子
Down here, we make big cases,
轰轰烈烈的大案子  就像Barksdale那宗 懂吗
Big hairy-balled cases like this Barksdale thing, right?
你们之前在辖区里干的所谓出警任务
And all that mess you call police work down in the districts...
那些个打打杀杀 小打小闹的一套
All that fuck-somebody-up and rip-and-run bullshit...
在这我们不兴这个
It won't play down here.
你们觉得我是在开玩笑
You think I'm kidding.
这玩意儿才能破案子 先生们
This is what makes cases, gentlemen.
这个
This!
记住了
Remember that.
干得好
Nicely done.
狗娘养的 从中饭开始我就等着了
Motherfucker, I been here since lunch, waiting.
他妈的屁都没出现
Ain't nobody been through here.
你听到我说的了吗?
You hear me?
我一直在等 可你们它妈的屁都不鸟
I been waiting and y'all ain't about shit.
够了 听着 听我说
Yeah, listen, listen to me.
瞧 如果你那么想 那么放下电话
Look, if you feel like that, then get off this phone...
来我这儿 大家单挑 小子
Come down here and step to me then, nigger.
嗯 好吧
Yeah, all right.
嘿 要是Roc-Roc十分钟内 不带着我的货出现
Yo, if Roc-Roc ain't here in 10 minutes with my re-up...
给我爆他的菊花!
Whoop his ass, man.
我知道你很久之前来过凶杀组
I understand you did a tour in Homicide years ago...
但是让我告诉你 我是怎么带这里的
But let me tell you how I run this unit,
因为这边我说了算
Because how I run it is how it runs.
我们执行严格的轮班制
We work on a strict rotation.
你在这待命 一旦有电话了 你就出警查案
You're up until you catch a call then you step down, work your case,
然后你后面的再上来
And someone else steps up behind you.
这就是我们的工作方式
This is the way we do business
在一个一年要发生250到300起案子的城市里
in a town with 250, 300 murders a year.
而且行之有效
And it works.
你不是给自己卖命 你是为我们干活
You do not play the game for yourself, you play it for us.
如果你能记住这么几条
If you remember these few rules...
你会发现我是个支持你 讲道理的人
You'll find me to be supportive and reasonable.
很有道理 长官
Very reasonable, sir.
他们都这么说我
That's what they say about me.
他们是这么说的 没错
They say that, they do.
嘿 Dink!
Yo, Dink!
你他妈的在搞屁啊!
What the fuck was that?
你一手那他们的钱 一手就给他们货?
You take a nigger's money, then you serve him?
搞什么飞机啊?
What the fuck?
我是说 你拿了他们的钱
I'm saying, you take their money...
然后让他们到别处去 让别人给他们货
Then you send them round and let some other nigger serve.
你那种做法...
The way you doing it...
只要有人拍个照 就把你们全抓了
Someone snapping pictures got the whole deal.
听到了没?
You hear?
在这你们都得小心点 嘿!
We got to tighten up around here, yo!
Jimmy
Jimmy.
精彩的案子
Hell of a case.
我在报纸上全看到了
Read all about it in the papers.
你做得很好 小子
You done good, kiddo.
我得...
I gotta....
D'Angelo Barksdale指挥了在
D'Angelo Barksdale supervised distribution...
平房区大院内的非法毒品买卖活动  同时涉嫌
In the low-rise courtyards and was also involved...
带团伙属性的暴力犯罪
In the violence attributed to the organization.
同时 他被新泽西当局逮捕
Further, he was arrested by authorities in New Jersey...
涉嫌持有一公斤海洛因原料
In possession of a kilo of raw heroin
并企图在Baltimore销售
Intended for distribution in Baltimore.
他承认自己是合伙犯罪中的主犯
He acknowledges his role as a leading conspirator...
同时他仍处于始于1999年3月的
And is already on parole for two earlier counts of distribution...
两起贩毒罪的缓刑期间
Dating from March, 1999.
你的量刑请求是?
What are you asking here?
由于Barksdale仍有两项罪名在身
As Mr. Barksdale has two prior convictions
同时坚称购买这些毒品
And is insisting that the effort to purchase...
并运输这些毒品 是由他一手策划
And transport the kilo was done on his own behest...
并拒绝和警方合作 交代案件其他同谋
And is refusing to cooperate against others in the conspiracy...
州政府提出执行最高的刑期
The state is offering only the maximum allowable
20年 法官大人
20 years, Your Honor.
Levy先生
Mr. Levy,
你已经清楚了此项认罪协议吗?
This is your understanding of the plea agreement?
是的 大人
Yes, sir.
那么很好 Barksdale先生
Very well then, Mr. Barksdale.
- 你能听清我说的吗? - 是的
- Can you hear me distinctly? - Yes.
此刻你是否清晰 有无受到酒精...
Are you now under the influence of alcohol....
- 那个Wee-Bey 伙计... - 进展如何?
- Wee-Bey, man. - How'd it go?
终生监禁 不得保释
For life, no parole,
他承认自己做了Orlando
He puts himself in for Orlando...
并企图谋杀Greggs
And the attempt murder on Greggs.
他还认了Nakeisha Lyles Deidre Kresson
Then he also takes Nakeisha Lyles, Deidre Kresson,
两起死于同一把手枪的公房区谋杀案
The two project murders that match that gun...
两个打劫小子 还有Little Man
Both the stick-up boys, and Little Man.
Little Man?
是的 尸体在Druid山公园 爬虫馆的后面发现
Yeah, body found up behind the reptile house in Druid Hill.
我想 他交代这些只是为了好玩
He gave us that one just for fun, I think.
他还承认谋杀了William Gant
He also takes William Gant.
我知道 这是胡扯
I know, it's bullshit.
他怎么说的
How'd he tell it?
伙计
Man.
- "崩" - 他是说贴着头?
- Boom. - He said a contact wound?
- 是的 - 不是那回事
- yeah. - It doesn't play.
Gant没有压迫伤 没有火药残余颗粒
Gant had no compression, no stippling.
伤口在前额 Bey是在放屁
Wound was to the front. Bey's talking out of his ass.
我知道 但这个狗娘养的 就是有一桩认一桩
I know, but this motherfucker's just taking murders just to take them.
他开枪打了警察  反正都要终身监禁 不得假释 管它呢
He's taking life, no parole, for shooting a cop, what the fuck?
替Bird抗下杀了Gant的罪又何妨
Might as well try to spring Bird for killing Gant.
全体起立
All rise.
天啊 我都干了些什么
Jesus, what the fuck did I do?
你现在开心了 贱人?
You happy now, bitch?
你这有卖海量的吗?
Are you the man with them jumbo sixes?
你它妈的想要多少?
How many you fucking want?
要个三 四百左右吧
Take about three or four hundred.
该死
Damn.
一切都在游戏里 呵呵
All in the game, yo.
都在游戏里
All in the game.
没错 但是我不觉得...
Right, but I didn't think--
当然了
For sure.
火线重案组 第一季 完